quoteland.com 2000-12-16

# Quoteland/Flycast Privacy Statement

* * *

### Quoteland.com/DoubleClick Privacy Policy

Quoteland.com, DoubleClick and its advertisers are deeply committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. Below is information outlining our continued support for the responsible management of consumer information.

**Consumer Information**

During the process of delivering an ad to you, Quoteland does not collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address. However, Quoteland does obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the Internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for example). The information collected by Quoteland is used for the purpose of targeting ads and measuring ad effectiveness on behalf of our advertisers.

In some cases, you may voluntarily provide personal information in response to a specific ad (this ad may ask you to fill out a survey or provide your zip code). If this does occur, Quoteland may collect this information on behalf of an advertiser. This information is used by an advertiser to respond to your request. In addition, Quoteland may combine this information with other users' information and review it in an aggregate form to understand the type of individuals who view a specific type of ad or visit a particular kind of website.

**Your Rights**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. Our third-party advertising company also separately places or recognizes a cookie file on your browser in the course of delivering advertisements to this Site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [click here.](http://www.sonar.com/content/privacy.htm)

* * *
